You know, the culture here. You know,
the guys, obviously Shep being the DC,
just being going, you know, 5 years with
him now. And then obviously Dan, you
know, this this the organization, this
coaching staff here. And you know, some
of the guys, you know, I just just
wanted to send it back again. And then
like I said, love being here. This is
home for, you know, my family and I and
my daughter. She's a little [crying]
little cranky cuz it's her nap time. See
if mama will take her here real quick.
So, now it's you know, like I said, it's
a blessing and excited to be back and
you know, stay close to home here. Shep
has always kind of pounded the table
[clears throat] saying you are a
starting NFL linebacker. Like he's
always said that whether injury before
or after. Just what does it mean to have
that belief in your defensive
coordinator and just all the experience
you have?
>> Yeah, I mean it's just one of those
things where, you know, like I said, we
started started off with him in that
room. So, he's seen it from day one and
it's one of those things where just to
have that confidence as me as a player
just wants to, you know, even play
harder for him. And I you know, for my
family just go out there and just prove
him right. And also just physically,
what what felt most unusual to use your
word last year coming off the injury and
when did things start to feel normal
again? Yeah, I would just want to say it
was like trying to I guess warm the knee
up. It was just a lot of stiffness that,
you know, I felt that was unusual of me
usually. So, now I would say like in the
off season, I would say couple weeks
after the season kind of giving it like
a full break, kind of getting back to
normal after that. So, just kind of so
those things you just you work so hard
and you rehab so hard like you don't
really take a break and then, you know,
obviously that little break after the
season it helped and you know, getting
back to training now just everything
feels smooth and you know, right back to
normal. You talk about continuity a lot
and usually it's with the offensive line
or maybe the secondary, but
how much does that apply to the
linebacker room as well? I mean, you've
been around Jack for a few years and and
Derek for even longer. Just just be able
to, you know, play with the three of you
together, you know, is is there a a
chemistry element there that's valuable?
Yeah, you know, it's one of those things
where, you know, we've all taken a lot
of snaps and, you know, I play with
those guys and you know, just the type
of communication the linebacker room has
as a defense. It's you know, it's our
job to, you know, communicate to the
whole defense, you know, the call and,
you know, the adjustments here and
there. So, it's one of those things
where, you know, communication plays a
big part, you know, and you know,
playing with those guys for a couple
years now.
Uh it would be good. Can you speak a
little bit just to your your growth as a
player? I mean, we all remember you as a
rookie, but in your eyes, how much
you've grown and in what areas? You
know, where are you a a better different
player?
>> Yeah, I mean, it's just one of those
things like, you know, coming in rookie
year, you know, trying to kind of make a
name for yourself. But now it's just
like obviously being a leader, you know,
in the locker room or rather on the
field just, you know, being that guy
that, you know, steps up to the plate or
uh making plays here and there. So, it's
one of those things where, you know, I
like to, you know, go out there and, you
know, do my best and play for the next
guy next to me. So, it's one of those
things where the linebacker room we take
it as, you know, a big deal for us to
play for each other.
Now the team has said a couple times
this is Jack Campbell's defense. Now
that Alex is gone, what about Jack's
makeup and what you've seen from him
over the last couple years?
>> Jack's
Yeah. No, Jack's a phenomenal guy, you
know, that guy he he puts he puts
definitely the work in and you know,
he's [snorts] one of those things he
knows the whole defense. He
goes in and out and you know, he man
doesn't sleep during the season at all
at night, you know, just
you know, putting himself in those
situations. So, for him to, you know,
take the hold of defense, you know, it's
guys see that, you know, we all feel
that and, you know, all year we've seen
it from, you know, first hand and then
seeing how he operates throughout, you
know, meetings and, you know,
walk-throughs and all that good stuff.
So, no, Jack's he's a phenomenal dude.
He's a even better guy. He's going to be
a father soon. So, congrats to him and
Megan on
a new baby coming soon. And I'm excited
to
be next to Jack. What do you anticipate
your off season look like and how has
maybe your your regimen or just the way
you approach things changed over your
years in the league?
Um yeah, it's one of those things where
obviously this off season was a little
different, you know, going into it um
being fully healthy, not rehab but, you
know, still working on some things I
wanted to fix. And you know, for the
most part I want to say just, you know,
getting healthy for the most part, you
know, it's
going to year five. Uh it really takes a
toll on your body playing this sport,
you know, I love the sport. But it's one
of those things where, you know, just
going into, you know, a new season fully
healthy, it feels good. Can you speak to
the confidence of the defense now? You
talked about being fully healthy the
last couple years, man, there's been so
many different injuries that got at you
guys out. But
coming into this year, why do you guys
feel like you can get it back on track
just as a defense? Um yeah, I think it
just puts it in perspective like uh
you know, injuries do happen, you know,
it's
you know, it's part of football, part of
this game. But it's just one of those
things trying to, you know, do little
stuff in the off season to, you know,
make sure those injuries don't happen
again. So,
uh it it'll be good to, you know, get a
new, you know, strength staff and all
that, you know, they do a phenomenal job
doing all this research. So, I'm excited
to, you know, get back to work with them
and uh come in and see the whole team
work. Now when you when you when you
think about your game at your best and
and when you're playing to your peak
capabilities, what do you feel like you
can add to this defense as a fully
healthy component?
Yeah, you know, uh fully healthy, I
mean,
I mean, I'm
I pride myself in the run defense, you
know, stopping the run game. And then
the pass defense, uh
you know, doing whatever coaches ask me
to do like covering anybody. So, it's
one of those things where, you know,
coming fully healthy, uh it would be,
you know, nice to see me out there, you
know, flying around and kind of doing my
thing again. Are you and Tevaughn still
fixing basements?
Uh I think so. Yeah, we're actually
we're actually talking about that where
we're where we're training at right now
in Florida. So,
he's trying to get me some more
basements going down there in Florida.
Follow up to that, I mean, you were in
here last year when Derek was talking at
his press conference. You you said that
he's on the hook for smacks in the
linebacker room. [clears throat] How did
he do and then are you back on the hook
for it?
>> No, no, he's still he's still definitely
on the hook, you know, he's got a little
more cheddar to me right now. But no,
he did a good job, you know, he he kept
the stock waters and all that. So,
I can't wait wait wait to be back in
that room with those guys. One of the
things Shep brought to the table as a
coordinator last year was kind of
handing the keys more to you guys with
with the checks and the adjustments.
You know, you didn't get to play the the
full load of snaps, but why why does
that player control level on the field,
how does that suit your game? Yeah, I
mean, it's one of those things the
linebackers, like I said, we take
control of the defense, we make the
calls, you know, it's kind of Shep put
on us to whatever we see, we can we can
check out of it and get the defense to
that check. So, he put a lot of you
know, a lot of faith in us and, you
know, we have a lot lot of faith in
Shep, too. So, it's one of those things
we got each other's back.
Does it feel like you're entering year
five here? Like does it feel longer or
shorter?
>> it's crazy how how fast it's gone. Going
from rookie year and obviously when I
signed seeing that rookie or the Hard
Knocks show up, I was like, "Oh my
gosh." Just like different features in
my face and obviously seeing Shep. I
mean, it's just crazy how fast this this
time definitely goes.
Speaking of Hard Knocks, new deal you
got your eye on? Particular set of
boots?
Uh you know, I'll have to see what kind
of style I got this off season. So,
we'll see if I got some new boots or
some new hats rolling in.
Hey, Alim McNeill talked about it a
little bit.
You guys are going to Germany this
season. I don't know, how do you how do
you feel about that? Uh it'll be it'll
be a fun trip, I'm sure. I'm sure it'll
be
sure I'll have to ask Saint to what all
the good spots around there are. So, got
to try some German beer. So,
>> [laughter]
>> never tried it before, so I'll be
definitely sure to ask him.
All right, thanks, guys. All right,
thank you. Appreciate it. Thank you.
>> [music]
[music]
>> Oh.
>> [music]
[music]